Oh my. I'm surprised to
see someone else here.
You by yourself?
Yes.
The Tarasque Swamp isn't a
place for a normal person...
Particularly not alone.
You seem to be implying you're not normal.
I simply possess a magic
item that nullifies poison,
and holy water that drives Tarasques away,
as well as an accurate map.
I'm after the Dragonblood flowers.
You don't mind if I take some, do you?
Sure.
Yeah, I'm surely the one who's not normal.
A Strange Man
and a Strange Job
Is that all you need?
Yes.
My mistress wants the
Dragonblood flower itself.
The medicine you make from
these will last a while,
but the flowers themselves won't
if they're plucked, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry for prying, but
is your mistress badly ill?
Yes, I suppose so.
I'd like to stay by their side,
taking care of them.
I know this doesn't help, but...
I hope they get better soon.
Thank you.
I and my mistress were fortunate I
was able to make your acquaintance.
I was just looking for someone
who could bring us Dragonblood
flowers at regular intervals.
It's silly to be asking this now,
but you're an adventurer, aren't you?
I'm Rentt Vivie. A
Bronze-class adventurer.
Bronze-class?
Have you changed your mind?
Not at all.
I'm certain you're strong enough.
If the pay and conditions are to your liking,
I would appreciate it if you would accept.
All right.
We'll make the arrangements
after our return, then.
Oh, I haven't introduced myself.
I'm Isaac Hart.
As for my mistress...
I'll introduce you after the
arrangements are finalized.
I didn't realize you were so strong.
Not many people come back
from that swamp unharmed.
Actually, this mask is just
a way to hide my identity.
I'm actually a Mythril-class adventurer.
Make sure you hire me next time!
I'll give you a discount!
Rentt!
I'd like to return this magic bag and
hire someone to butcher a monster.
Butcher...?
Did you defeat one?
There's a lot.
Okay.
I'll show you to the Butcher's, then.
A monster doesn't just drop magic stones.
Their bodies can be butchered to
provide many different materials.
I learned how to do the basics myself when I
was learning to be a hunter in the village,
but for things I can't handle, I pay
the money to hire a specialist.
Dario!
Hey!
What's up?
Rentt here has brought
something unusual for us.
A Tarasque!
A Tarasque?
Okay, bring it out!
Will Edel be okay?
Edel's resistant to poison.
It's big.
And in good shape, too.
Not a single wound on the shell.
That's rare.
Is it?
Yes.
The normal way to fight
one of these is to attack
from outside the range of
its poison to weaken it.
So the shell always gets damaged.
I see.
You killed it in basically
a single hit, didn't you?
A single hit?
I just didn't have time
to land multiple hits.
Don't be so humble!
I haven't seen a Tarasque
of this quality in ages.
Will it be worth a lot?
Of course.
Can I ask you to handle it?
Yes.
Look forward to it.
Thanks.
I guess I'll go to the orphanage tomorrow.
Thanks for staying out so late with me.
Not at all.
Anyway, Rentt, you've gotten
a lot stronger, haven't you?
Have I?
You defeated that huge
Tarasque all by yourself!
You're at the high end of Bronze...
No, you could easily be Silver!
You should remember that.
I do feel stronger, but...
But saying that I, myself, have
gotten stronger feels weird.
Isaac doesn't seem to be an adventurer,
but he's probably got the strength of a
Silver-class, or probably close to Gold.
I just took advantage of my undead body.
This strength is something I got
just by becoming a monster.
Of course, I want to go back to being human.
But without this power, I'll go
back to who I was then, right?
10 years... 10 years!
With no talent, no improvement...
Where putting in effort each
day was all I could do...
Could I go back to that and
still try to become Mythril?
This is fine. I've got just the thing.
Perfectly done.
What's perfectly done?
The job.
Already?!
This is it...
I've never seen it before.
It's beautiful!
This is wonderful.
It's rare to see one that's
been prepared so well.
Is it?
The only adventurers who go to the Tarasque
swamp are of fairly high rank, right?
They should all know how
to properly prepare herbs.
Well, just because of the
kind of place it is,
there's not a lot of time
to do things properly.
Sometimes you can get attacked
by a Tarasque on your way out.
You must be a powerful adventurer.
I'm Umberto, the healer.
And this is...
Norman. An herbalist.
Wow, with something of this quality
I can make a medicine to treat
Malaccumula really quickly.
Really?
Yes. If there's any left over, can I use it?
There are people who need it.
Of course. I don't mind.
Do you want more?
Of course...
I'd be lying if I said I didn't.
Is this enough?
No need to pay me. Just put it to good use.
You sure? This would be
worth a lot of money.
It's nice to just help
people, once in a while.
Thank you. This is wonderful.
I'll be able to save so
many lives with these...
We can't repay you right now,
but if you need something
in the future, tell us.
I will.
And there we go.
This completes the job.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you.
No...
I'm the one who has to thank you.
I can't thank you enough!
I was going to become an adventurer and
get it myself if nobody took the job...
But I don't think that would've worked.
You no longer want to be an adventurer?
I actually want to be one even more.
Rentt...
I want to be an adventurer like you!
One who can help people!
Like me?
Thank you so much!
I can't do anything to thank you, but if...
There's nothing I can do
to help you, is there?
That's not true.
There are times when I need help, too.
When that happens, I'll come to you.
Great! You'd better!
Sure.
Was everything okay?
Alize, you said there were sometimes
small monsters in the basement, right?
Yes. That's right.
Edel's old gang will protect you.
Gang... Of puchi suri?
That's great!
Thank you, Edel!
That's so great...
I wonder if I'll be able to tame monsters
like this when I become an adventurer.
Anyway, if you want to be an adventurer,
you should start training early.
Training?
The guild holds classes.
And I can train you too, when I have time.
Really?
If you have mana, you should
learn to use magic, too.
But I don't have money...
It's expensive to train with a sword,
but training to learn magic
costs even more, right?
I've got a friend who's not
doing anything with her time.
Don't worry about it.
That won't do!
I can't count on you for that much.
Then I'll lend you the
money, with no interest.
When you become an adventurer and
start earning money, pay me back.
I'll pay it back with interest.
Fine.
We have a deal, then.
I look forward to doing
business with you, Rentt!
I don't mind teaching her.
There are indeed times when
I'm "not doing anything."
As you say.
Sorry... I meant when you're free.
You should be careful with your words.
You don't understand how young girls feel.
Thanks for the warning.
I have very few interactions
with young girls, though.
Come on, that's not true.
There's a young girl you know quite well.
See?
Where?
I just remembered about this extremely
powerful spell I just developed...
L-Lorraine?
Let's see just how much that
undead body of yours can take!
Wait! You're young!
You're very young, Lorraine!
Your skin is as fair as driven snow...
And your statuesque figure...
Even the water fairies created
by the goddess of beauty
as the physical manifestation of
her virtue would bow their heads
at the sight of your gorgeous face!
You are the very picture of a young
girl in every way, Lorraine!
Where the hell did you
learn to talk like that?
Don't tell me you say that
to every girl you meet.
Of course I don't!
I mean...
I just said what I was thinking.
You'd like a little more to eat, right?
Uh...
I'll bring you something.
I split the pots between the one
with blood and the one without.
I think that got to me a little...
Why am I the only one working
when I'm the master?
Rentt!
Morning!
Can we talk?
This way.
What's this about?
Um, Rentt, did you know anyone
in the Latour household?
The Latour household?
You don't?
I've never heard the name.
There's actually a job
requesting you specifically.
Oh, the one from Isaac?
So you do know them?
No...
I just know a man who I assume is a
servant of this Latour Household.
Is the family that famous?
I'd like to think I know most of
what there is to know about Maalt.
I know little about them, myself.
They're not nobles, but they're a very old
house with a lot of influence over Maalt.
Someone of my lowly station
wouldn't be told any more.
So they're very secretive.
Each generation's guild master
is told to be very careful
not to offend the Latour household.
Rentt, if you're going to live here in Maalt,
you absolutely cannot refuse
a request from the Latours.
I have no intention of refusing.
But... is it okay?
Um... you're...
If they find out I'm a
monster, they'll kill me.
It's going to be hard.
No, when I met Isaac, he didn't
seem to care about my appearance.
If it was an issue, he wouldn't
have made the request at all.
All right.
But if there's any problem at all, tell me.
Of course. I'll start
by paying them a visit.
We've come to talk about
your condition today.
You're sick with Malaccumula.
So it's as I thought.
I'll need to tell the Church
to send a replacement.
There's no need.
What's this?
A medicine made from Dragonblood flower.
Take one pill a day.
Little by little, it will dissolve
the foulness building within you.
I appreciate it, but this
is so expensive, and I...
Headmistress Lilian, you don't
need to worry about the money!
So please...
Please get better soon!
Alize...
Umberto, don't tell me
you got this flower...
I did used to be an adventurer, but
somebody like me could never do that.
An adventurer took the job from Alize,
for the price of one bronze piece.
I see...
It was the one who came
here that day, wasn't it?
Excuse me... is Isaac in?
Yes. He's in the mansion.
Please, go inside.
It looks like there's a maze...
Yes. Be careful.
Even if I was told to come here for a job?
Yes.
Do maps cost money?
There'd be no point in having one.
A special magic item was
used to make this garden.
The path changes.
There's an item that can do that?
No... even if it exists, that's incredible!
The heads of the Latour family have
always collected magic items.
I'm told that this item was
a part of their collection.
I don't like the fact that I have to
make it past one of their hobbies.
Even if I told you there's a reward?
A reward?
Those who make it through the
maze and reach the mansion
can receive a magic item from
the head of the household.
Really?
The entrance to the maze is only opened
rarely, at the whim of the head of household.
I'm sure that's the case today.
Thanks for telling me.
One more thing...
I'd like to ask something from someone who
I assume has completed the maze himself.
Yes?
Any advice?
Let's see...
The sun won't help you. I suppose
that's enough of a hint.
The sun?
Thank you.
They're giving me a magic item.
Of course I'm going to try it.
Even this cursed mask is a magic item...
And it wouldn't be cheap
if I bought it normally.
If I can get a powerful magic item...
I need money and equipment if I'm
going to become Mythril-class, too!
No luck, huh?
Even though a magic item made this place,
I suppose it won't work since it's not a labyrinth.
That's fine. I've got a
good sense of direction.
I can draw a mental map that's more
than enough for a maze of this size...
I'm totally lost...
The Garden Labyrinth